Guide to the Institute for the Future Reports M1186
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Accession 2017-188 (Boxes 13-48)
  - The Telecommunications Industry Mittman, Robert Goldberg, JoAnne, 1986-12-01 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Medical Equipment and Supplies Industry (CDC) Mittman, Robert Poulin, Mary, 1985-12-01 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Electronic Information Services (CDC) Mittman, Robert Lucas, Barbara G., 1985-10-01 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "Electronic Information Services (CDC) Revised" Mittman, Robert Lucas, Barbara G., 1986-02-01 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Consumer Electronics (CDC) Mittman, Robert Saffo, Paul, 1985-09-01 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "Consumer Electronics (CDC) Revised" Mittman, Robert Saffo, Paul, 1986-03-01 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications Equipment (CDC) Mittman, Robert Goldberg, JoAnne, 1985-11-01 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "Telecommunications Equipment (CDC) Revised" Mittman, Robert Goldberg, JoAnne, 1986-02-01 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Components (CDC) Mittman, Robert, 1985-11-01 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - "Electronic Components (CDC) Revised" Mittman, Robert, 1986-03-01 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Computer Integrated Manufacturing Mittman, Robert, 1986-08-01 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
  - Looking Ahead at American Health Care Amara, Roy Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Poulin, Mary Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1986-03-01 (Box 23, Folder 10-15)
  - Looking Ahead at American Health Care Amara, Roy Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Poulin, Mary Morrison, J. Ian, 1952-, 1987-06-01 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
  - Profiting from Teleconference Use (Outlook Project) Johansen, Robert, 1986-07-01 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Lumber, Wood and Secondary Wood Products in California (State of California) Mittman, Robert, 1986-10-01 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Global Opportunities Bardin, Stephanie Mittman, Robert Saveri, Andrea Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Wayne, Jennifer C., 1994-05-01 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - California Health Safety Net Databook, 1994-12-01 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Woodland Public Library, Strategic Planning Databook (Woodland Public Library) Kaplan, R. Ozawa, Nancy Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1995-06-01 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Woodland Public Library Workshop, Strategic Choices, July 25, 1995 (Woodland Public Library) Kaplan, R. Ozawa, Nancy Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1995-06-01 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Access Excellence, Electronic University, Summit ’94, Pioneer Class (Genentech) Nagai-Rothe, Tomi O'Hara-Devereaux, Mary Ozawa, Nancy, 1994-06-01 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Woodland Public Library Kaplan, R. Ozawa, Nancy Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1995-11-01 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - California’s Local Libraries Kaplan, R. Ozawa, Nancy Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1996-04-01 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - The Future of California’s Health Care, The Rise of Managed Care and the Collapse of the Safety Net (Kaiser Family Foundation) O'Hara-Devereaux, Mary Mittman, Robert Falcon, Rod, 1996-02-01 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - "Selecting and Using Communications Tools (generic version of 3Com Workshop report)" Saveri, Andrea, 1994-12-01 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Toward a Light-Touch Economy, 1999-09-01 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Notes on Seminar on Future Broadband Communications Baran, Paul, 1970-02-01 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - A Case Study Using Forecasting as a Decisionmaking Aid Enzer, Selwyn, 1969-12-01 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Simulation of Urban Systems - A Selected Bibliography Nagelberg, Mark, 1970-01-01 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Selected Urban Simulations & Games Nagelberg, Mark Little, Dennis L., 1970-04-01 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - A Collation of Similar Delphi Forecasts Sahr, Robert C., 1944-, 1970-04-01 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Models And Simulation - Some Definitions Little, Dennis L., 1970-04-01 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - A Method of Obtaining Forecasts for Long-Range Aerospace Program Planning Becker, Harold S. De Brigard, Raul‏, 1970-04-01 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Delphi and Cross-Impact Techniques Enzer, Selwyn, 1970-06-01 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Considerations on a Framework for Community Action Planning Becker, Harold S. De Brigard, Raul‏, 1970-05-01 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Factors in the Introduciton of a New Communications Technology Into Syria and Turkey LeCompte, Gare, 1970-08-01 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Toward the Institutionilization of Change Wilson, Albert George, 1918- Wilson, Donna, 1970-08-01 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - STAPOL A Simulation of the Impact of Policy, Values, and Technological and Societal Developments upon the Quality of Life Little, Dennis L. Feller, Richard, 1970-10-01 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - STAPOL Simulation - Game Manual Little, Dennis L. Rochberg, Richard Feller, Richard, 1971-03-01 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - STAPOL Appendix to the Simulation - Game Manual Little, Dennis L., 1970-10-01 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Simulation, Futurism, and the Liberal Arts College Little, Dennis L. De Brigard, Raul‏, 1971-04-01 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Some Trends Likely to Affect American Society in the Next Several Decades Little, Dennis L. Johnson, Theodore, 1971-04-01 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Multipurpose Planning Games Helmer-Hirschberg, Olaf, 1971-12-01 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - The Automobile Insurance System Enzer, Selwyn Slotsky, Gorgon J. Little, Dennis L. Doggart, James E. Long, David A., 1972-02-01 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Toward a Framework for Communications Policy Planning Lipinski, Andrew J., 1971-12-01 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Business Potential of Teleconferencing in Canada Lipinski, Andrew J., 1974-01-01 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Some Societal Impacts of Alternative Energy Policies Enzer, Selwyn, 1975-06-01 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Emerging Societal Issues Amara, Roy Johansen, Robert Lipinski, Andrew J. Samuel, Patricia A., 1943- Spangler, Kathleen, 1975-07-01 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Some Methods of Futures Research Amara, Roy, 1975-12-01 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tort Reform Schmid, Gregory, 1940- MacMillan, Bruce, 1976-04-01 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - The Future of Hunting and Gun Control Lipinski, Andrew J., 1975-07-01 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Health Education MacMillan, Bruce Palmer, Michael, 1977-11-01 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Educational Programs for the Elderly McNulty, Maureen Palmer, Michael, 1977-12-01 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - The Programatics of Long-Range Planning Johansen, Robert Samuel, Patricia A., 1943-, 1977-03-01 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Education With Reduced Expectations McNeal, Barbara Johansen, Robert, 1978-10-01 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - National Service in the U.S. Nyhan, Michael J. Palmer, Michael, 1979-05-01 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - A Scenario Approach to Assessment of New Communications Media Spangler, Kathleen Johansen, Robert Valle, Jacques, 1977-07-01 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Futures Workshops Tydeman, John Lipinski, Hubert M., 1980-12-01 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Technology Assessment of Videotex and Teletex / Phase 1 Report Tydeman, John Zwimpfer, Lawrence Lipinski, Hubert M. Nyhan, Michael J. Plummer, Robert P., 1981-05-01 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Technology Assessment of Videotex and Teletex / Standards Policy Workshop Background Papers, 1981-06-01 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Telecommunications and Service to the Developmentally Disabled / Volume 1, 1979-04-01 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Telecommunications and Service to the Developmentally Disabled / Volume 2, 1979-05-01 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Telecommunications and Service to the Developmentally Disabled / Volume 3, 1979-07-01 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Testing and Evalutating a Teleconference Model as a Management Tool in the Planning Process, 1981-04-01 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Ten Years of Teleconferencing, 1981-12-01 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - User Needs Workshop Johansen, Robert, 1983-06-01 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Future Growth of Real GNP Lipinski, Andrew J., 1983-06-01 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Looking Ahead at American Health Care, 1986-02-01 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Looking Ahead at American Health Care, 1986-07-01 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Assessing Teleconferencing Needs Charles, Jeff, 1989-03-01 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Innovation and Advanced Development in the Computer Industry Rosing, Wayne, 1989-07-01 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Demistifying the Innovation Process Johansen, Robert, 1989-07-01 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Governing Local Communities in 2040 Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1989-07-01 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Report on Forecasts Relevant to Owens-Corning Fiberglas Corporation’s Long-Range Environmental Forecast (OCF) Gordon, Theodore J., 1969-08-01 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Analysis of the EPRC Responses to Forecasts about Development in Higher Education (EPRC) Gordon, Theodore J., 1969-08-01 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Report on Forecasts of Educational Administration (NCPEA) Gordon, Theodore J. Sahr, Robert C., 1944-, 1969-09-01 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut’s PPB System and the Forecasting of Social Indicators (CRC) Gordon, Theodore J., 1969-12-01 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The AT&T Long-Range Study, Volume 1 Baran, Paul Lipinski, Andrew J. Rochberg, Richard Judd, Peter, 1970-01-01 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - The AT&T Long-Range Study, Volume II Baran, Paul Lipinski, Andrew J. Rochberg, Richard Judd, Peter, 1970-01-01 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Current Research on Cross-Impact Analysis Techniques (IFTF) Rochberg, Richard, 1970-01-01 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Education Report to EPRC (EPRC) Sahr, Robert C., 1944-, 1969-08-01 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Summary Report to EPRC (EPRC) Gordon, Theodore J., 1980-03-01 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - A National Environmental Information Agency Judd, Peter, 1970-06-01 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Attering Foundation Study on Potential New Ventures (Kettering) Helmer-Hirschberg, Olaf Helmer, Helen, 1970-06-01 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Report of Work in Progress Baran, Paul, 1970-07-01 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Some Prospects on Residential Housing by 1985 (OCF) Enzer, Selwyn, 1970-07-01 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - A Forecast of the Development of Facsimile Newspapers (NSF) Gordon, Theodore J. Rochberg, Richard, 1970-06-01 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - The Indices of Technological Change (NSF) Andrews, Catherine W., 1970-06-01 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - The Future-State-of-the-Union Reports Progress Report (Russell Sage) Helmer-Hirschberg, Olaf, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Cross-Impact Operating Instructions Richtmyer, Peter, 1971-08-01 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - The Future of Communications Regulation as it Affects the Data Processing Industry (IBM) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1971-09-01 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
  - Effect of Canadian Policies with Respect to Computer/Communications on the Participation of U.S. Industry in Canada, 1970-1985 Lipinski, Andrew J. Lipinski, Hubert M., 1971-11-01 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Effect of Canadian Policies with Respect to Computer/Communications on the Participation of U.S. Industry in Canada, 1970-1985, Supporting Appendices (CTF) Lipinski, Andrew J. Lipinski, Hubert M., 1971-11-01 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Toward a Study of Future Urban High-Capacity Telecommunication Systems Baran, Paul, 1971-12-01 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - ARPA Policy-Formulation Interrogation Network, Quarterly Report (ARPA) Baran, Paul Lipinski, Hubert M. Randolph, Robert H., 1972-06-01 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - ARPA Policy-Formulation Interrogation Network, Semiannual Technical Report (ARPA) Baran, Paul, 1972-10-01 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - ARPA Policy-Formulation Interrogation Network, Semiannual Technical Report (ARPA) Baran, Paul Lipinski, Hubert M. Miller, Richard Randolph, Robert H., 1973-04-01 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Development of a Computer-Based System to Improve Interaction among Experts, First Annual Report Amara, Roy Vallee, Jacques, 1973-08-01 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Project AWARE, Volume I, Executive Overview (Scott Paper Company version) Amara, Roy Enzer, Selwyn Lipinski, Andrew J., 1973-07-01 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Project AWARE, Volume I, Executive Overview (Lever Brothers version) Amara, Roy Enzer, Selwyn Lipinski, Andrew J., 1973-07-01 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Project AWARE, Volume I, Executive Overview (Monsanto version) Amara, Roy Enzer, Selwyn Lipinski, Andrew J., 1973-08-01 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Project AWARE, Data Base Summaries (Multiclient) Amara, Roy Enzer, Selwyn Lipinski, Andrew J., 1973-08-01 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - ARPA Policy-Formulation Interrogation Network, Semiannual Technical Report (ARPA) Vallee, Jacques Johansen, Robert Lipinski, Hubert M. Miller, Richard, 1973-09-01 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Development of a Computer-Based System to Improve Interaction among Experts, Second Annual Report (NSF) Amara, Roy Vallee, Jacques, 1974-08-01 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Value and Attitude Changes Resulting from an Energy Crisis Lipinski, Andrew J., 1974-08-01 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - ARPA Policy-Formulation Interrogation Network, Final Report (ARPA) Vallee, Jacques Lipinski, Hubert M. Miller, Richard, 1974-12-01 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Assistance on Special Interests and Explorations (Rockefeller Foundation) Amara, Roy, 1975-01-01 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Project AWARE Issue Summary, Future Corporate Communications (Multiclient) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1975-01-01 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Project AWARE, Some Long-Term Changes of Importance to American Can Company Enzer, Selwyn, 1975-01-01 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Some Corporate Impacts of Alternative Energy Policies (Uniroyal Foundation) Enzer, Selwyn, 1975-04-01 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Alternative Allocation Formulae for General Revenue Sharing, Preliminary Report (NSF) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Lipinski, Hubert M. Palmer, Michael Wilson, Thaddeus, 1981-12-01 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Project AWARE, Consumer Expenditures in 1985—with Implications to Monsanto Lipinski, Andrew J., 1975-04-01 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Report of Results, INCO Seminar on Latin America, Held on May 12-13, 1975 (INCO) Amara, Roy Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1975-05-01 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Future of Hunting and Firearms Possession in the United States (Remington Arms) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1975-06-01 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - An Alternative Approach to General Revenue Sharing Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Lipinski, Hubert M. Palmer, Michael, 1975-06-01 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Long-Range Planning in an Operational Context Johansen, Robert Samuel, Patricia A., 1943-, 1975-06-01 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Conservation-Minded World of 1990 (Monsanto) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1975-10-01 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Development of a Computer-Based System to Improve Interaction among Experts, Final Report (NSF) Vallee, Jacques, 1975-09-01 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Project AWARE, Financial Opportunities in Food-Related Aspects of Agribusiness (Chase Manhattan) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1975-09-01 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Project AWARE, Future Domestic Banking Environment (Chase Manhattan) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1975-09-01 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Project AWARE, Future International Banking Environment (Chase Manhattan) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1975-09-01 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Project AWARE, Consumer Expenditure and Savings Patterns in 1985 (Chase Manhattan) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1975-09-01 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Future Consumer Behavior and Expenditure Patterns (Honda Motor Company) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1975-11-01 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - An Assessment of Some Political and Social Risks of Investment in South Africa (International Nickel Company of Canada, Ltd.) Amara, Roy Samuel, Patricia A., 1943-, 1976-01-01 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Monsanto Senior Management Lipinski, Andrew J., 1976-01-01 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Future Consumer Behavior and Expenditure Patterns (Remington Arms) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1976-01-01 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Investment Opportunities in Food Production in Developing Countries (Monsanto) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1976-02-01 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - The Basic Telephone Set Lipinski, Andrew J., 1976-02-01 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Long-Range Effects of Agricultural Chemicals Lipinski, Andrew J., 1976-02-01 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - "Computer-Based Communication in Support of Scientific and Technical Work (NASA) Final Report" Vallee, Jacques Wilson, Thaddeus, 1972-04 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Future Scenarios Lipinski, Andrew J., 1976-04-01 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Alternative Operating Worlds for 1985 (AT&T) Lipinski, Andrew J. Palmer, Michael Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1976-03-01 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Alternative Operating Worlds for 1985 (Celanese Corporation) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1976-03-01 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - The Future Housing Market Lipinski, Andrew J., 1976-06-01 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Future of Regulation Lipinski, Andrew J., 1976-07-01 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Guide to Telecommunications Policy, A Compendium of Contributing Individuals and Organizations (AT&T) Chula, Margaret Lipinski, Andrew J. Muzzicato, Jeanne, 1976-09-01 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Auto Accident Liability (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Reform) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- MacMillan, Bruce, 1976-10-01 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - AT&T’s Future Environment (AT&T) Lipinski, Andrew J. Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Palmer, Michael, 1976-11-01 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Priorities in Postsecondary Education (The Arthur Vining Davis Foundations) Palmer, Michael Chula, Margaret, 1976-11-01 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - A Look at the Future of Regulation (Monsanto) Lipinski, Andrew J. Spangler, Kathleen, 1976-11-01 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - The Future of Beverage Container Deposit Legislation (Monsanto) Palmer, Michael, 1976-11-01 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - The Camelia Report, A Study of Technical Alternatives and Social Choices in Teleconferencing (Charles F. Kettering Foundation) Johansen, Robert Vallee, Jacques, 1976-12-01 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Disposable Packaging Lipinski, Andrew J. MacMillan, Bruce, 1976-12-01 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Review of Candidate Industries for Potential Acquisitions (Celanese Corporation) Amara, Roy, 1976-12 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Future Government Control of Feedstocks, Part II (Monsanto) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1977-04-01 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Future Societal Developments and Postsecondary Education (Lilly Endowment, Inc.) Johansen, Robert Samuel, Patricia A., 1943-, 1977-01-01 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - A Study of Patterns of User Behavior and System Acceptance in Computer Conferencing (Bell Northern Research) Vallee, Jacques Lipinski, Hubert M. MacMillan, Bruce Wilson, Thaddeus, 1977-02-01 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - The Crosswalk Exercise Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-02-01 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - The No-Fault Experience in Other States, Auto Option Paper #1 (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Reform) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-03-01 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - The No-Fault Experience in Other States, Auto Option Paper #2 (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Reform) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-03-01 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Comparative Negligence, Auto Option Paper #4 (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Reform Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-03-01 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - The Uninsured Motorist, Auto Option Paper #5 (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Reform Palmer, Michael, 1977-04-01 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Coordination of Benefits, Auto Option Paper #6 (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Reform Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-04-01 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - System Reforms Short of No-Fault, Auto Option Paper #3 (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Reform Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-04-01 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Words as Predictors of Social Movements, A Preliminary Exploration (Monsanto) Spangler, Kathleen, 1977-03-01 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - The Investment Climate in the Western Hemisphere (Celanese Corporation) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-04-01 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - The Domestic Banking Environment over the Next Five Years (Chemical Bank) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Palmer, Michael, 1977-04-01 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Alternative Futures and Postsecondary Education in Pennsylvania (Buhl Foundation and Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities) Johansen, Robert McNulty, Maureen, 1977-06-01 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - No-Fault Legislation in California, 1971-1977 (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Re­form) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-05-01 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - A Michigan-Style No-Fault Reform in California (California Citizens’ Commission on Tort Reform) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-05-01 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - World Climatic Change and Variability, 1977-1990 Amara, Roy Lipinski, Hubert M. J., 1977-06-01 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - The Insurance World of 1990 Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Amara, Roy, 1977-06-01 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Interim Report on World Climatic Change and Variability (ARPA and National Defense Uni­versity) Amara, Roy Lipinski, Hubert M., 1977-07-01 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - The Future of Sunday Supplement (Standard Gravure Corporate) Jalonen, J., 1977-07-01 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - The Insurance World of 1990 Amara, Roy Palmer, Michael Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-07-01 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Extended Field Tests of Computer Conferencing (NSF) Vallee, Jacques Johansen, Robert Lipinski, Hubert M. Spangler, Kathleen Wilson, Thaddeus, 1977-09-01 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Future Housing Market, Update (Monsanto) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-08-01 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - An Investigation of Computer-Based Communication in the Geosciences (NSF) Vallee, Jacques, 1977-10-01 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Future Product and Service Opportunities (The Continental Group) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1977-10-01 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Background for the CAC Presentation (Monsanto) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Palmer, Michael, 1977-10-01 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Stages of Growth Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Palmer, Michael, 1977-11-01 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - The Intermedia Project Johansen, Robert Vallee, Jacques Spangler, Kathleen Shirts, R. Garry (Robert Garry), 1934-, 1977-11-01 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Group Communication through Computers, Volume 5 Johansen, Robert DeGrasse, Robert Wilson, Thaddeus, 1977-11-01 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Health Education MacMillan, Bruce Palmer, Michael, 1977-11-01 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Educational Programs for the Elderly (AVD) McNulty, Maureen Palmer, Michael, 1977-12-01 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Societal Monitoring Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1977-12-01 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - A Survey of Permanently Installed Teleconferencing Rooms in North America (AT&T) Johansen, Robert McNulty, Maureen, 1978-05-01 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Institute for the Future/Arcata National Palmer, Michael, 1978-04-01 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Forecasting Attractive Acquisition Areas, Part I Palmer, Michael, 1978-05-01 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Forecasting Attractive Acquisition Areas, Part II Palmer, Michael, 1978-06-01 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Forecasting Attractive Acquisition Areas, Part III Palmer, Michael, 1978-06-01 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Forecasting Attractive Acquisition Areas, Part IV Palmer, Michael, 1978-06-01 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Forecasting Attractive Acquisition Areas, Part V Palmer, Michael, 1978-07-01 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Interactive Group Modeling (NSF) Lipinski, Hubert M. Amara, Roy Spangler, Kathleen Traweek, Sharon, 1978-07-01 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Background for the CAC Presentation (Monsanto) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Russell, Lawrence, 1978-10-01 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - The Future Characteristics of an Extended Processor (IBM) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1978-12-01 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Entry-Level Labor Force by Geography and Residency, 1985-1990 (AT&T) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1978-12-01 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Entry-Level Labor Force Slippage in Test Scores (AT&T) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1978-12-01 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Macro-Environmental Scenarios (Aetna Life & Casualty) Schmid, Gregory, 1940-, 1979-01-01 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - The Future of the United Kingdom (multiclient) Lipinski, Andrew J., 1979-02-01 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Identifying Future Attractive Businesses, Part I (Saga Corporation) Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Palmer, Michael Amara, Roy, 1979-02-01 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Identifying Future Attractive Businesses, Part II Schmid, Gregory, 1940- Palmer, Michael Amara, Roy, 1979-04-01 (Box 36, Folder 1)